uh Donald Trump's Supreme Court nominee
Neil Gorsuch or as I'm referring to him
banderson
Cooper faced his second confirmation
hearing today it's a very good thing
this is Comedy Central because he came
ready to bring with the laughs people
take a look she could teach a monkey how
to read I think she did I wrote this 800
page book on makes a great door stop
gift for Christmas I cut a really bad
deal on royalties robe does mean
something to me and not just that I can
hide the coffee stains on my
shirt all
right he's he already disobeying the
Constitution because these jokes are
cruel and unusual
punishment comedians he's clearly aiming
for a career as a standup so as a comedy
club MC I would like to introduce Neil
guch Emily uh give it up for your bar
and weight staff they all just lost
their health insurance
punch